{
    "subject": "Cliff_Robertson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Cynthia_Stone",
    "human_readable": "Cliff Robertson is married to Cynthia Stone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884260892868042,
            "question": "Is Cynthia Stone married to Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9515761137008667,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Cliff Robertson and Cynthia Stone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9501405954360962,
            "question": "Name the person Cliff Robertson is married to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190658330917358,
            "question": "Who is Cliff Robertson married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8973299264907837,
            "question": "To whom is Cliff Robertson currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8467103838920593,
            "question": "Who is Cynthia Stone married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7267562747001648,
            "question": "Who are Cliff Robertson and Cynthia Stone related to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6937965750694275,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6757672429084778,
            "question": "What is the name of Cliff Robertson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6476927399635315,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Cliff Robertson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cliff Robertson is married to Cynthia Stone.",
            "html": "yago_2492_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Cliff Robertson's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_2492_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Cliff Robertson?",
            "html": "yago_2492_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Cliff Robertson and Cynthia Stone related to each other?",
            "html": "yago_2492_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2492_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that they were married from 1957 to 1960, indicating a past relationship rather than a current one.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Cliff Robertson is married to Cynthia Stone\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because multiple documents mention that Cliff Robertson was married to Cynthia Stone from 1957 until their divorce in 1960. Document 42.txt also confirms this information, stating that \"Robertson then was married to Dina Merrill from 1966 until their divorce in 1989; they had one daughter, Heather. Robertson was married to Cynthia Stone from 1957 until their divorce in 1960; they had one daughter, Stephanie.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Cliff Robertson was married to Cynthia Stone from 1957 until their divorce in 1960, and mentions they had a daughter named Stephanie. This supports the triple that Cliff Robertson is married to Cynthia Stone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}